Guide to the Grace Mott Johnson Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Other Papers, 1802-1979; Series III; 5.01; (13 boxes)
  - Photographs
    - Margaret Dasburg, Paris, and Germany, 1886-1887, 1945 (Box 29)
    - Unsorted, 1908-1926, undated; 17 (Box 30)
      Photographs of farmland, cows, horses, unidentified people, and souvenir photographs
    - Photographs of Grace Mott Johnson's paintings and sculptures, 1920-1931, undated; 11 (Box 31)
    - Photograph of sign for Andrew Dasburg group exhibition, 1915 (Box 31)
    - Negatives of Andrew Dasburg's paintings, undated (Box 31)
- Printed Material, 1829-1957; Series IV; 1.67; (4 boxes)
  Not arranged in any particular order.
  The Printed Material series includes documents, such as catalogues and notices, relating to Grace Mott Johnson's exhibitions. The series also includes clippings Johnson collected. The series is largely comprised of publications belonging to the Johnson and Van Cleve families.
  - Catalogues and exhibition notices of Grace Mott Johnson's shows, 1929-1936, undated (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous catalogues saved by Grace Mott Johnson, 1879-1936 (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous pamphlets, undated (Box 32)
  - Clippings, notes, business cards, and invitations, undated (Box 32)
  - Ladies' Album belonging to Harriet Gilley, 1831 (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous clippings sent by Grace Mott Johnson to Alfred Dasburg, 1950s (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1920s-1950s; 2 (Box 32)
  - Railway clippings and pamphlets, 1847-1891; 3 (Box 33)
  - College of the City of New York, examination papers, 1873 (Box 33)
  - Discourses and Addresses at the Ordination of the Rev. Theodore Dwight Woolsey, 1846 (Box 33)
  - Cruise of School-Ship "Mercury" in Tropical Atlantic Ocean, 1870-1871 (Box 33)
  - History of the United States belonging to Fanny Johnson, 1852 (Box 33)
  - Pathfinder Railway Guide for the New England States, 1850 (Box 33)
  - New York and the White Mountains, 1852 (Box 33)
  - American Railway Guide, 1851, 1853 (Box 34)
  - Burke's Illustrated Guide: Niagara Falls, 1858 (Box 34)
  - How Americans may avail themselves of the advantages of Stuttgart, Germany, 1890 (Box 34)
  - University, 1888 (Box 34)
  - Josiah Willard Gibbs & George Westing-House, The Hall of Fame for Great Americans, 1957 (Box 34)
  - Academy Notes, 1916 (Box 34)
  - Morse's New Atlas of the United States, 1823 (Box 34)
  - Map of the Clinton Line Railroad, undated (Box 34)
  - Map of Northern Part of Illinois, undated (Box 34)
  - Physical Map of Africa, undated (Box 34)
  - The Lord's Prayer in 53 Languages, undated (Box 34)
  - A Word: He That Has Ears, Let Him Hear, 1882 (Box 34)
  - Modern Atlas, on a New Plan; To Accompany the System of Universal Geography, 1829 (Box 34)
  - The Greek Slave, clipping, undated (Box 35)
  - Postcards, undated; 5 (Box 35)